The body of a young Black man named Trey Reid, a 21-year-old student at the predominant white Delta State College in Mississippi, was found hanging from a tree, his arm broken and his leg broken.
We should all be furious.
And I don't mean all Black people.
I mean anybody who has desired a semblance of civility and humanity in this country.
However, I want you to know that there are forces at work that want to draw you out, that want to ensnare you with your own righteous rage so that they can be given reason to entrap you.
This is not a conspiracy theory.
This is watching the systems and the forces work.
I want you as well to feel your feelings instead of reacting to them.
Because we're not even ready when you see folks arguing about why they should feel compassion for someone who does not see them as worthy.
So may we lift up this young man, his soul, his spirit, lift up his people.
And again, when I say we, I don't mean just Black people.
I mean anyone whose values in humanity and morality are sunk deeper than the roots of the tree he hung from.
And there seems to be far too little of that on our media, in our government spaces, and even in our group chats.
May we lift up Trey and every other Black individual who has been lynched in the myriad ways that this nation manages to find to do so.
Please reflect this evening and tomorrow starts your day honoring the life of Trey and all of those who came before him with the same fervor that you have honored the life of an individual who did not honor the life of anyone who didn't think like him.
Thank you.